<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>

    <template id="about_us" name="About Us">
        <head>
            
            <style>

                <!-- css code for slider--> .myslides {display: none } <!-- css code for end of slider--> .dropdown{ position: relative; display:
                inline-block; } .dropdown-content { display: none; position: absolute;
                background-color: #000000; min-width: 160px; box-shadow: 0px 8px 16px 0px
                rgba(0,0,0,2) ; padding: 12px 16px; color:white } .dropdown:hover .dropdown-content{
                display: block; } </style>
            <title> online vegetable store </title>
        </head>

        <body>
            <table border="0" width="100%" height="60%" bgcolor="#000000">
                <tr>
                    <th align="center">
                        <img t-att-src="'/fresh_shoppers/static/src/img/Fresh Shoppers1.png'" />
                    </th>
                    <td>
                        <input type="text" placeholder="Search for Products"
                            style="width:250px; height:30px;" />
                        <input type="button" value="search" style="width: 120px; height: 25px;" />

                    </td>
                    <th>
                        <a t-attf-href="/website/fresh/home/page">
                            <font color="white"> Home </font>
                        </a>
                    </th>
    
                    <th>
                        <a t-attf-href="/website/fresh/contact/us">
                            <font color="white">Contact</font>
                        </a>
                    </th>
                    <th>
                        <font color="white"> Shop here</font>
                    </th>
                </tr>
            </table>

        <p>
            Welcome to Fresh Shoppers. This is Best Store for fresh vegetables and fruits. <br>
                </br> We are here talk aout this system. this Stysem Stands for Online
            vegetavle store. we provide vegetable Fruits to consumer. they can buy thier goods
            according to thier choice or need. <br>
                    This module consists of information about the products and services. this
            includes
                    two sub-modules, Product master and Price master.

                </br>
            We hope you enjoy our products as much as we enjoy offering them to you. If you have any
            questions or comments, please don't hesitate to contact us. Sincerely, Name, [title, ie:
            CEO, Founder, etc.] <br>
                </br> With one part of the pie, i.e. sourcing complete, Jagsfresh was
            founded in the year 2017, independently to add value to the produce that finally reaches
            the customer under controlled conditions. The produce available at Jagsfresh is
            significantly fresher, without residue and has the highest shelf life across all retail
            channels. </p>  
        <p>
                Jagsfresh has been sourcing over 600 types of Fruits and vegetables across the
            world, with
                strong sourcing strength and relationships with progressive farmers following
            stringent
                good- farming practices. With growing customer base across Delhi/NCR, more than
            10,000 other
                household products have been offered to our customers.
            </p>
            Today, Jagsfresh is present at all levels - grass root sourcing, Value add, temperature
            controlled logistics, last mile delivery. Jagsfresh has been operating from state of the
            art facilities, to create value, keeping in mind the nutritional needs of our customers. <br>
            </br>
        <br>
            </br>
        <br>
            </br>
               <div >
                <img t-att-src="'/fresh_shoppers/static/src/img/Banner2.jpg'"
                    width="65%" height="12%" style="margin-left:17%"/>
            </div>


            <div >
                <img t-att-src="'/fresh_shoppers/static/src/img/slider3.jpg'" width="80%" style="margin-left:10%"/>
            </div>

        <footer>
                <p style=" color:green; font-family:sans-serif;">"All Right Reserved By Aman,Anubhav Goel,Abhishek" </p>
            </footer>
        </body>
    </template>
</odoo>